positive comes in the negative end go
out the positive end you got make the
second how it work anyway so but if you
take that spark lead off any one doesn't
matter or just a coil one um okay and
have it pulsing you can put it down to
the negative terminal on the battery and
will jump
to you can put it to the positive
terminal and jump to but you can
also um the Caps where it produces
hydrogen and oxygen you can also put it
put it down to the caps and it is
attracted straight in doesn't detonate
the gas I don't know why people are
trying to use that spk to try and make
HD or no and you go bang because you
don't just an idiot anyway or
misunderstood or
misrepresented you know the info so you
can screw them out screw the Caps out
and hold the spark and don't have to go
to any it'll go to the liquid and down
into the liquid onto the plat and
produce more gas than you could without
anything you can go just comes back out
anyway now I can take that spark goes
for everything you know all your
insulators you seen that all your
insulators underneath your Bonnet like
your radiator hose and your belts and
your fuel lines and your that spark
jump It's attracted into them mhm and if
you got five times insulated wires it
goes through the five times insulation
yeah so where's the insulation for that
kind of space
the only insulation is to actually make
it go
somewhere it's in yes like jump in and
go through the inside of the metal yep
they give it a pass but it doesn't go
elsewhere yeah and well if you
disconnect it off the um uh you know off
a spark plug it'll jump from the center
of the coil straight down to ground
Earth negative on the coil won't it yeah
it it won't go
anywhere all right won't go to the
positive side but what I did find out is
that
with this with the gas in the air
conditioning okay now this is L of gas
and when it's primed up and I'm not sure
about the earlier gas but if you take
that spark plug one now see the commodor
run the
V6 okay so that is um but it's it's
running way management do you
understand that SS double firing yes yes
is a white here
yes I'm over in the Sun
hiding um so if you hold it and and the
insul in your air condition you got an
insulation Rubber and flixy rubber y if
you hold it real close nothing happens
if you hold it right away nothing
happens but if you hold it and pull it
out to exactly 1
in okay that one in it attracts to the
rubber that one
in right on that one the engine
go
stop nothing else under that Bonnet with
that spark will stop that car
Well the lady about five minutes what do
the answer press that button presses
anyone who is
[Music]
it she's not dropping in there um so
what happened is that now on the
aluminum tubing M you just go straight
to any of that and the car stops no no
matter whether you an inch or anything
it just stops the car so at this time
you're running pressure in pressure in
you know um vacuum side because you got
a vacuum and the pressure doesn't matter
which side MH what actually happens is
the spark itself is in Earth okay okay
it is neutral it's positive and negative
at the same time which cancels them man
this that's really what you're going to
see here opposites M and the opposite of
opposites is equilibrium you I'm
understand that mhm so opposite of North
is South opposite of South is north but
opposite of both is equilibrium yeah so
we get those together now Tesla made the
coil and the spark and everything gos
and it'll go through a few lines in one
out the other jump in the other one out
and everything it'll go through every
single thing around the car it also is
if you have a those spk good if you had
that spark um uh on a piece of metal
that'll bite you but it's a very
interesting thing because you um you put
your hand on the mud guard and aim that
spark to the side of the mud guard and
get really close and it one jump to you
and it'll jump to the mugard but you
don't feel a single thing that's the
greatest converter out of of your
um well that don't understand it but
from AC to DC DC to AC and and neutral
to neutral nothing in other words a
biing spark at the coil knock you over
absolutely
nothing just takes it to something
don't anyway beside all that doesn't
matter you're thinking so the the air
conditioning has shown that it still
happens I tried it the other day it's
still happening years and years later so
what's happening is you got an iner gas
okay inside the isn't it it's an iner
type gas in the air
conditioner fairly heavy composition of
yeah different chemicals yeah it well
says that
stainless okay this one here gets a bit
of rust on it it come straight off it's
supposed to non-rust or you know but
it's composition of M different things
what all R yeah which one day
okay so now the sun keep
moving um so but the um the gas in there
and everything else is attracting right
through the metal and right through the
rubber into it it's attracting the um
the spark and the two inert ones
actually
combine and they don't blow doot in your
computer or your alternator or anything
else could you just go straight around
hit the car get start it
they won't they go against all of that
it's not it's not a a thing known and it
shuts the car down instant you go and
hit the key again start it okay and you
do it again it shut the C straight away
but nothing else does you can go around
every other bolt and nut and screw and
rubber and H everything around that car
every warre want to shut the car down
the only one will is that gas in
condition and he did this with the old
gas and 3 4 a and you did this on point
ignition you said and electronic
ignition it
work okay yeah and the the VT Commodore
that pet a videotape and everything
girls Tri them all different other
things but on that we run out of gas so
now the air conditioner isn't working
but it's still got a vapor in there
right so I haven't tried it for about uh
who knows probably about 8 months or
more because air condition didn't work
on
inside so all I did was um the other day
went back to it put Don Bing shut the
car down F now the air condition
was I'm stumping everything go okay but
that's logical anyway because it was
this lady just to get this this this
older lady turned up here um a few
months ago no two months ago she said
that she had acquired like sell off
Peter he says not but sell off Peter and
put onto a vehicle and then she tried to
reach Peter and could and could and
could and then she had it strapped or
somebody strapped it to the air
conditioning rubber with a zip tipe now
what they didn't realize is when she
hooked it up that way her air
conditioning was still pumping but the
air conditioning don't work I had to
sell her that and I said soon as you got
off cuz she called me the girl from
somebody told her whether it was Peter
or somebody else and he said it wasn't
him but she says it was I don't know two
sides of any sort so or somebody else
but I said soon as you disconnected that
cell off the air conditioning I said
your air conditioning would have work
against you it did she said you're not
funny I said no it changes and that that
frequency going in can actually stop um
the gas from actually
freezing like a fridge it changes the
whole ofuure
so back to this now so there's a funny
thing happen see a normal magnet even
NEOS but a normal Neo that that's an
iron is it it's a coated G coated iron
flaming washer now doesn't matter iron
or anything go steel or anything else
that'll attract to either side okay you
can just turn will go either it's not
determinable to right it'll just do it
so North and South Pole doesn't come
into attraction and repulsion against
said I need another magnet or a
different kind of
metal you went quite for anyway so now
within that if I put on either side what
happens is the washer becomes powerful
very
powerful
okay and the other side of the magnet
really isn't see but the washer
is now opposite
attract
so we get rid of that washer is cut
locked on and we put our do track yep
now what'll happen now is that one go to
that
washer that goes to the
outside that goes to the outside it
won't go to that washer you understand
mhm so now what you shouldn't be able to
do is take one of them doesn't matter
which one because you got four poles in
this you turn that around to the way
that they don't come together so they
push and you just walk
in and you do put them
together that's positive
side so I'm going to turn it and make
the negative
side okay there little buggers he gives
me something all me fingers are busted
and I can't would you like to have some
little ones Joe no h these some Feld do
it for you yeah I know these
won't now these won stick on properly
because it's the wrong combination of oh
and the W with the thick thickness and
everything else but that's close enough
but what happens now is there opposites
right they're trying to get off cuz he's
out of alignment inside and outside M
and difference but what happens is Bingo
and just try pull
Aang on go right
on tiny
little swap that washer over CH yeah do
it with a big one
yeah it's a little bit
bigger so normal that's how they will
come together that's North and South
together trying go to the
washer not
sideways yeah W go W go come on got to
now we turn one of these and it doesn't
matter which way we turn that around we
get them together and
then go to the
washer quite strong quite strong right
it's not noisy strong no but what it's
what it's actually done is um
it's weakened these outers and it's pull
them in to a different
angle okay so you're
getting you're getting the outside poles
which are as strong as the you know
either side roughly but negative is the
North Pole and the negative
start